HO VAN CHIEN

Front-end Developer

MAIN OBJECTIVE

Looking for opportunities, challenges in career, orientation to become a professional Frontend Developer in assigned work. With over 1.5 years of experience, I will use my skills and knowledge to create valuable products for my customers. From there, contribute to the development of the company. And my goal in the next few years is to become a full-fledged developer.

EDUCATION

Cao Thang Technical College

Major: Information Technology - Software

SKILLS

- Soft skills: Teamwork, critical-thinking, collaboration.
- Programing languages: Javascript, Typescript.
- Front-end Technologies: ReactJS, NextJS, Sass, Webpack, GraphQL, Apolo.
- Dev Tools: Git, Docker, Github, GitLab, Firebase, Figma, Photoshop, Jira, VS Code, Zsh, Bash.

REACH AT ME:

Call: (+84) 073 239 783 Mail: hvchien216@gmail.com Skype: hvchien216@gmail.com Ho Chi Minh City, VietNam

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Dinovative | May 2021 - Present

Maua app - MauaPay

- · Collaborate with team members.
- Integrating API with GraphQL.
- Pickup requirements, analyze, discuss with the team to tackle them.
- Do peer review to help teammates improve code quality and check the correction of dependencies and the system.
- Invoke in an Agile team.
- Technology: ReactJS, GraphQL, Material-UI, Redux, Webpack, Gitlab.

VietinBank iPay

- Collaborate with team members.
- Pickup requirements, analyze, discuss with the team to tackle them.
- Do peer review to help teammates improve code quality and check the correction of dependencies and the system.
- Invoke in an Agile team.
- Technology: ReactJS, Redux, HTML5, Scss, Webpack, Gitlab.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

K-group | Oct 2020 - May 2021

GT-Link

- · Collaborate with team members.
- Pickup requirements, analyze, discuss with the team to tackle them,
- · Database design discussion.
- Invoke in an Agile team.
- Technology: ReactJS, Ant-Design, Redux, Webpack, Docker, Github.

FRONT-END INTERN

iBenefit | Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

- · Collaborate with team members.
- \bullet Work in a React Native Framework to building an internal calling application for the company's business with the support of the leader
- Pickup requirements.
- Develop some features in the company's CMS project.
- Technology: ReactJS, React-Native, Redux, Github.

SIDE PROJECTS

E-COMMERCE

https://e-commerce-fullstack.vercel.app

- Description: This is an e-commerce website have integrate api Stripe.
- Technology: NextJS, Typescript, Material-UI, NodeJs, MongoDB, Redux-Saga.

E-COMMERCE

https://tfm-react.firebaseapp.com/

- Description: This is an e-commerce website cloned from tfm.vn, with the help of a friend in charge of the Backend part.
- Technology: ReactJs, HTML, CSS3, SCSS, Material UI, Redux, Django Framework.